{
    "id": "1ec638051b6243f8969a76d7c961fe79",
    "title": "Demonstrative and interrogative pronouns exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0aeb715fc65746d9b7b8d13572637819",
            "title": "Demonstrative And Interrogative Pronouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………… is that boy sitting next to Peter?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Who",
                        "Which",
                        "What"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… was a horrible experience.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Which",
                        "That"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… are our children.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "This",
                        "These",
                        "What"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… is the road that leads to the railway station?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Which",
                        "Who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… told you this story?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Who",
                        "Which",
                        "What"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. do you mean?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Which",
                        "That"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. shall we invite to preside over the function?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Whom",
                        "Which",
                        "What"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… is your phone?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Where",
                        "Which",
                        "That"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Are the people living in a village happier than …………….. living in a town ?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "those",
                        "these",
                        "they"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… is your father?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Who",
                        "Where",
                        "What",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. is the house that belongs to my grandfather.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "This",
                        "Which",
                        "Where"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………… shall we contact?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Whom",
                        "What",
                        "Which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}